{
  "swedish": [
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Arbeta",
      "rightAnswer": "jobba",
      "wrongAnswer": ["hoppa", "leka", "springa"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Löpa",
      "rightAnswer": "springa",
      "wrongAnswer": ["hoppa", "leka", "arbeta"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Skutta",
      "rightAnswer": "hoppa",
      "wrongAnswer": ["springa", "leka", "arbeta"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Anteckna",
      "rightAnswer": "skriva",
      "wrongAnswer": ["läsa", "måla", "rita"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Promenera",
      "rightAnswer": "gå",
      "wrongAnswer": ["simma", "sova", "köra"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Teckna",
      "rightAnswer": "rita",
      "wrongAnswer": ["måla", "klippa", "klistra"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Färglägga",
      "rightAnswer": "måla",
      "wrongAnswer": ["rita", "klippa", "skriva"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Klistra",
      "rightAnswer": "limma",
      "wrongAnswer": ["klippa", "rita", "skriva"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Konstruera",
      "rightAnswer": "bygga",
      "wrongAnswer": ["riva", "klippa", "leka"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Tvaga",
      "rightAnswer": "tvätta",
      "wrongAnswer": ["städa", "bära", "sortera"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Finna",
      "rightAnswer": "hitta",
      "wrongAnswer": ["simma", "sova", "köra"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Förtära",
      "rightAnswer": "äta",
      "wrongAnswer": ["dricka", "sova", "leka"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Klunka",
      "rightAnswer": "dricka",
      "wrongAnswer": ["äta", "sova", "hoppa"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Snyfta",
      "rightAnswer": "gråta",
      "wrongAnswer": ["simma", "sova", "köra"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Tralla",
      "rightAnswer": "sjunga",
      "wrongAnswer": ["dansa", "hoppa", "spela"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Klot",
      "rightAnswer": "kula",
      "wrongAnswer": ["docka", "bil", "bok"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Kofta",
      "rightAnswer": "tröja",
      "wrongAnswer": ["sko", "väska", "cykel"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Fordon",
      "rightAnswer": "bil",
      "wrongAnswer": ["boll", "docka", "bok"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Roman",
      "rightAnswer": "bok",
      "wrongAnswer": ["bil", "boll", "docka"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Skepp",
      "rightAnswer": "båt",
      "wrongAnswer": ["bil", "cykel", "väska"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Bädd",
      "rightAnswer": "säng",
      "wrongAnswer": ["stol", "bord", "soffa"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Lärosäte",
      "rightAnswer": "skola",
      "wrongAnswer": ["hem", "parken", "affär"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Föda",
      "rightAnswer": "mat",
      "wrongAnswer": ["dryck", "penna", "boll"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Grönområde",
      "rightAnswer": "park",
      "wrongAnswer": ["hem", "skola", "affär"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Butik",
      "rightAnswer": "affär",
      "wrongAnswer": ["hem", "skola", "park"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Jycke",
      "rightAnswer": "hund",
      "wrongAnswer": ["katt", "häst", "fågel"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Vän",
      "rightAnswer": "kompis",
      "wrongAnswer": ["fiende", "hund", "bok"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Springare",
      "rightAnswer": "häst",
      "wrongAnswer": ["katt", "hund", "fågel"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Planta",
      "rightAnswer": "växt",
      "wrongAnswer": ["bil", "penna", "cykel"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Fjäderfä",
      "rightAnswer": "fågel",
      "wrongAnswer": ["katt", "häst", "hund"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Skär",
      "rightAnswer": "rosa",
      "wrongAnswer": ["blå", "gul", "grön"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Vacker",
      "rightAnswer": "fin",
      "wrongAnswer": ["ful", "liten", "snabb"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Jättelik",
      "rightAnswer": "stor",
      "wrongAnswer": ["liten", "smal", "tunn"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Kvick",
      "rightAnswer": "snabb",
      "wrongAnswer": ["långsam", "tråkig", "seg"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Saktfärdig",
      "rightAnswer": "långsam",
      "wrongAnswer": ["snabb", "arg", "alert"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Munter",
      "rightAnswer": "glad",
      "wrongAnswer": ["ledsen", "arg", "trött"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Sorgsen",
      "rightAnswer": "ledsen",
      "wrongAnswer": ["glad", "lycklig", "trött"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Förbannad",
      "rightAnswer": "arg",
      "wrongAnswer": ["glad", "lycklig", "trött"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Utmattad",
      "rightAnswer": "trött",
      "wrongAnswer": ["pigg", "glad", "arg"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Alert",
      "rightAnswer": "pigg",
      "wrongAnswer": ["trött", "glad", "arg"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Kraftig",
      "rightAnswer": "stark",
      "wrongAnswer": ["svag", "skör", "liten"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Skör",
      "rightAnswer": "svag",
      "wrongAnswer": ["stark", "kraftig", "stor"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Het",
      "rightAnswer": "varm",
      "wrongAnswer": ["kall", "glad", "stor"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Vid",
      "rightAnswer": "bred",
      "wrongAnswer": ["smal", "tunn", "hög"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Tunn",
      "rightAnswer": "smal",
      "wrongAnswer": ["bred", "rolig", "hög"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Skrämd",
      "rightAnswer": "rädd",
      "wrongAnswer": ["modig", "glad", "trött"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Lyssna",
      "rightAnswer": "höra",
      "wrongAnswer": ["tala", "skriva", "gå"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Ropa",
      "rightAnswer": "skrika",
      "wrongAnswer": ["viska", "sjunga", "skratta"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Frusen",
      "rightAnswer": "kall",
      "wrongAnswer": ["varm", "mjuk", "blöt"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Sväva",
      "rightAnswer": "flyga",
      "wrongAnswer": ["gå", "simma", "köra"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Förmögen",
      "rightAnswer": "rik",
      "wrongAnswer": ["fattig", "snål", "svag"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Lasarett",
      "rightAnswer": "Sjukhus",
      "wrongAnswer": ["skola", "affär", "teater"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Slunga",
      "rightAnswer": "kasta",
      "wrongAnswer": ["fånga", "lyfta", "trycka"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Litteratur",
      "rightAnswer": "böcker",
      "wrongAnswer": ["filmer", "spel", "musikaler"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Bevittna",
      "rightAnswer": "se",
      "wrongAnswer": ["ignorera", "gömma", "röra"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Flyktig",
      "rightAnswer": "kort",
      "wrongAnswer": ["rädd", "lång", "trött"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Skicklig",
      "rightAnswer": "duktig",
      "wrongAnswer": ["trött", "klumpig", "ny"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Metropol",
      "rightAnswer": "storstad",
      "wrongAnswer": ["by", "förort", "landsbygd"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Autentisk",
      "rightAnswer": "äkta",
      "wrongAnswer": ["falsk", "kopierad", "imitera"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Utopi",
      "rightAnswer": "drömsamhälle",
      "wrongAnswer": ["storskog", "mardröm", "krig"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Eliminera",
      "rightAnswer": "ta bort",
      "wrongAnswer": ["lägga till", "behålla", "skapa"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Premiera",
      "rightAnswer": "belöna",
      "wrongAnswer": ["straffa", "ignorera", "förlora"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Spektakulär",
      "rightAnswer": "fantastisk",
      "wrongAnswer": ["tråkig", "vanlig", "intetsägande"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Inbillad",
      "rightAnswer": "inte sann",
      "wrongAnswer": ["god", "äkta", "smart"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Exklusiv",
      "rightAnswer": "ovanlig",
      "wrongAnswer": ["allmän", "dyr", "inkluderande"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Restriktion",
      "rightAnswer": "begränsning",
      "wrongAnswer": ["frihet", "möjlighet", "tillåtelse"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Diffus",
      "rightAnswer": "otydlig",
      "wrongAnswer": ["trevlig", "klar", "stillastående"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Effektiv",
      "rightAnswer": "verksam",
      "wrongAnswer": ["ineffektiv", "verkningslös", "slö"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Fundamental",
      "rightAnswer": "grundläggande",
      "wrongAnswer": ["sekundär", "obetydlig", "oviktig"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Kollektiv",
      "rightAnswer": "gemensam",
      "wrongAnswer": ["individuell", "ensam", "falsk"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Fnissa",
      "rightAnswer": "skratta",
      "wrongAnswer": ["gråta", "snyfta", "surra"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Klar",
      "rightAnswer": "genomskinlig",
      "wrongAnswer": ["mörk", "smutsig", "slarvig"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Byggnad",
      "rightAnswer": "hus",
      "wrongAnswer": ["bil", "cykel", "träd"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Slumra",
      "rightAnswer": "sova",
      "wrongAnswer": ["vakna", "klättra", "leka"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Studera",
      "rightAnswer": "undersöka",
      "wrongAnswer": ["skriva", "måla", "promenera"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Säte",
      "rightAnswer": "stol",
      "wrongAnswer": ["bord", "säng", "soffa"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Divan",
      "rightAnswer": "soffa",
      "wrongAnswer": ["matta", "bord", "säng"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Bostad",
      "rightAnswer": "hem",
      "wrongAnswer": ["skola", "parken", "affär"],
      "category": "noun"
    }
  ]
}
